Good morning, sleepyheads.
It is the final day of testing the top 10 tourist attractions in America.
Yesterday, we traveled all the way to the Grand Canyon, where we hiked and marveled
at the best views we have seen in our entire lives.
And today, we travel to Colorado to watch a concert at Red Rocks Amphitheater.
It is considered by many people to be the best concert venue in America.
It is once again a 4 a.m.
wake-up to catch our flights.
I am very excited to travel to Denver, Colorado with Haley.
Fine, let's go to the airport.
After 10 days straight of flying, I cannot believe we haven't been delayed even once.
And just when I'm going to thank Shopify for sponsoring this series, our flight gets
delayed severely.
This is not good, y'all.
This is bad.
This means we are at risk of missing our concert.
Our intercom's not working.
I'm not able to communicate with the flight attendant.
They're not even able to communicate with me.
We need to have that fixed.
I appreciate your patience.
I'll give you updates as I know.
Thank you.
Our flight has now been delayed nearly two hours but this guy must be the
real deal because he walked on the plane and within minutes we were boarding and
in the air on our way to Phoenix for a connection.
Our first flight is in the wrong direction but luckily I'm really fast and we
were able to get on our flight to Colorado for the final tourist attraction!
Yes!
We got a rental car to Drive places, Alpha move.
The final bucket list day, let's go to Denver.
Let's go!
Despite our delayed flights, we made it to Colorado with time to actually explore before
the concert.
You already know what that means.
We're going to find a cool structure downtown.
That is the state capital of Colorado.
We went inside, I bought stickers and a postcard.
Also a guy offered to take a picture of Haley and I when we were
in the middle and...
Let's just say he went off.
He kept offering to take more and more photos with different angles.
Honestly, they're all really impressive, so thank you.
Today's episode is kind of like the road trip Golden Gate Bridge episode where it's
a mixture of things.
Number one, Denver, Colorado.
It's the Mile High City.
There's Rocky Mountains.
It's beautiful.
Number two, Red Rocks Amphitheater.
This is a venue that people visit even if there's not a concert going on
because that's how beautiful it is.
And number three, Lewis Capaldi.
I can't believe we get to see him live.
He has so many bangers like exclusively hits our flight was late getting here.
So we don't have that much time Unfortunately to explore Denver.
However, first we need to go back there and take a picture next to the
one mile high marker
We drove over to a cool shopping area in downtown Denver called 16th Street, it's
a cool shopping area They have a hat store.
So naturally we entered with intentions to purchase a hat.
This one is a Red Rocks hat
We're going to Red Rocks later for a concert.
Nice.
Yeah.
Hailey and I made it to the shopping area.
We just purchased head accessories.
Not a ton going on right now because it just rained.
It's kind of raining a little bit still.
Hailey, this is a surprise, but I got us a dinner reservation at a really
cool restaurant, but it's at 4pm because we have to go to the concert kind
of early.
So I'm never bad about an early dinner.
Amen.
We need some snacks to hold us over.
We're going to Target.
Let's go.
Hailey and I just got our snacks.
Here's what we picked up.
I got a coconut water as a beverage.
We both got portable protein packs.
I got a peanut butter perfect bar.
And of course it is not a Target snack run without Joyride.
I found Fruity Zips and Fruit Chews here.
I have not been able to find these this entire trip.
As you know by now, Joyride Day is right around the corner.
It's June 13th.
Hopefully by now your calendars are marked, you've RSVP'd, and you're ready to go to
the store to set a new world record.
I'm going to be doing a 24 hour live stream on Joyride Day on my
channel as we try to break this world record.
So be there.
so fun.
It's me, Ryan from the future.
We're working on working on the 24-hour live stream set right now it's gonna be
way cooler and more built out on joyride day almost 40 000 of you have
already rsvp'd for joyride day i'll see y'all this saturday for the coolest 24-hour live
stream ever and if you go to target look for this in-cap display it has
rare joyride flavors it's the perfect photo op shout out to all the joyride runners
all around the country ohio texas new jersey new york tennessee florida the list goes
on thank you so much we're gonna go back to the car because we have
to drive to this dinner restaurant should we get jeans oh yes the lady at
the hat store did say it was gonna be really cold at Red Rocks because
it's higher elevation and it's kind of a chilly day the way she looked at
me when she saw my shorts I think it's highly recommended I get some jeans
let's go shopping and then we're going to dinner Haley is very scared that it
will be cold and rainy at the concert tonight so she picked out some jeans
okay the Sun has decided to come out here in Denver.
We'll see if that lasts, but we're going to drive to the dinner restaurant.
Haley has pants now.
Let's actually go.
We are listening to Lewis Capaldi songs and eating snacks on our way to the
restaurant.
I know it's probably unwise to eat snacks while actively embarking to dinner, but we
have had a very weird diet on this entire trip, so please don't judge us.
We made it.
It's that pink building.
Haley and I have arrived to our dinner reservation and it is at Casa Bonita.
It's right next to a Dollar Tree and Adventure Dental.
I don't think I want my dental vision and orthodontics to be that adventurous.
Your dental and vision?
Yes.
They do all three there.
Oh, that's nice.
I do want that.
Luckily, we have a reservation.
I'm not going to tell you too much about this restaurant.
Okay, fair enough.
I mean, just looking at the outside, I don't know what to expect.
The sun came out?
Maybe it's because we were listening to Lewis Capaldi.
His music's actually really sad.
But he does drop bangers.
He only has bangers.
True.
We walked into Casa Bonita with an open mind.
I heard this restaurant is full of surprises, though, so I'm kind of nervous.
But that went away when I saw how awesome it is in here.
Haley and I were seated in a booth near the back of the restaurant and
quickly served chips and salsa.
Casa Bonita is more like a theme park than it is a restaurant.
Every 15 to 20 minutes they have a new type of fun going on.
For example, arcade and gaming, merchandise and the dude from South Park.
Here's some context.
First of all, this is a 52,000 square foot legendary Mexican restaurant.
In 2003, South Park put it in one of its episodes.
17 years later, the owners filed for bankruptcy, but the creators of South Park bought
it and restored it for $40 million.
So yeah, there's also great live music and people diving into pools of water every
15 minutes.
I have a question for you, Ryan.
Okay.
Do you know what Bonnie, that means?
Yeah, it means Haley.
Beautiful.
More like Casa Haley.
More like Casa Haley because that's synonymous.
They mean the same thing.
Things started getting a little awkward and boring between Haley and I, so I decided
to spice things up by doing a little magic trick.
Whoa.
I thought I disappeared.
Yeah.
Really?
You thought I disappeared?
No, it looks really realistic.
Oh my gosh.
Haley's on my side now.
Yes, I am.
And I'm staring at these glistening sopapillas.
These are the dessert that comes with your meal.
They look delicious.
Let's try.
It's a fried dough with honey and cinnamon sugar.
And it's delicious.
Before we go to this concert, I think it's a perfect time to do some
pearlet tips.
I love superlatives.
We did this before we got to Hawaii on the 50 states series.
It's so fun to reflect on the adventure that we just had.
So number one, Haley, what is the best meal that we ate on the entire
bucket list series?
First, we ate barbecue at Disney.
That was delicious.
And then we got Ben's Chili Bowl in DC.
That was unreal.
Gordon Ramsay's Fish and Chips also stands out.
Oh, Stationery in Carmel by the Sea.
And the Dodger Dog definitely lived up to the hype.
But the New York City Dog lived up to the hype even more.
I think we can both agree Ben's Chili Bowl was the best meal?
Absolutely, as you speak with honey on your face.
Best stranger we met?
I gotta go with Jeff from Washington, D.C., our bike tour guide.
He was so cool.
But also Ben's mom at Ben's Chili Bowl.
She is 92 years old and she was cleaning up our table for us.
Yes, they're neck and neck.
Honestly, it's a tie.
Best souvenir that we bought?
Our favorite collectible.
I really did like my Mickey ears.
I gotta go with my I Survived New York City shirt.
Yeah, that one's really good.
Favorite photo from the entire trip?
Ooh, honestly, I really like the photo of us under the arch at Yellowstone.
Best view in America?
Grand Canyon.
Yeah.
Just as unbelievable as everyone makes it out to be.
Most unexpected moment?
Honestly, how I felt watching Hamilton.
When I was just sitting there crying, I was like, wait a second, what's going
on?
Yeah.
For me, I think it was the bison crossing the road at Yellowstone.
Oh, that's a good moment, too.
I knew you were going to like that one.
We could sit here and reflect all day, but you made scrapbook pages for each
of these days, so we can just do that for the rest of our lives.
Yeah, and pass it down.
This has been so much fun.
I just want to say again, thank you guys so much for watching the series
and hanging out with us this summer.
It's going to end at this concert, and then we'll have our rankings of the
top 10 tourist attractions in America.
Just like that.
It's time for us to drive to Red Rocks Amphitheater.
This was delicious.
Really fun dinner.
Let's go to a concert.
In just 17 minutes, Haley and I will be arriving to our final tourist attraction.
To say we're nervous is an understatement.
The stakes are high because today, Haley and I will crown a winner of the
number one tourist attraction in America.
We are now seeing Red Rocks in the distance, which can only mean one thing.
We've arrived.
Y'all, we made it to Red Rocks Amphitheater.
this right here for example is a red rock i don't know if that's the
one i don't think it is the amphitheater is just up ahead we're already hearing
noises that are musical which is very exciting also yes i just bought merch there
was a trading post they had all kinds of cool stuff i also got magnets
pins and this has to be the coolest postcard yet right that is so fun
i think it's made of wood.
Oh, it is.
Yeah, super thin.
Out of every single tourist attraction, this one has the highest percentage of five-star reviews.
Wow.
So what is all the hype about?
Jenny left a five-star review and said, amazing, amazed, and in awe entire time.
Everything was perfect, even the moon.
Five stars.
Well, don't get my hopes up.
Don't get my...
Kristen's review is a little more simple.
This place rocks, lol, laughing emoji.
Five stars.
Someone had to do it.
Somebody had to say it.
It's sitting right there, the opportunity to leave that pun as a review.
And Kristen took it.
Kristen got there first.
Red Ribbit said, Ribbit.
Best music venue in the country.
Did I mention it's the best?
It's number one.
Second to none.
Five stars.
This is crazy, but I think I just understood what second to none meant for
the first of my life.
That is pretty crazy.
Top two and it's not two is a similar way to kind of establish the
same premise with a different sort of approach.
That one clicks for me instantly.
I like that one.
top two and I'm not two.
I think the venue is opening very soon.
People are in line.
We should probably get in line as well.
Let's do this.
It's a beautiful evening for the final day.
Even the walk up to the entrance of this venue is a beautiful experience.
We caught up to the crowds and scanned our tickets for the concert.
Look at this place, y'all.
There's already so many people here.
Being here in person is truly remarkable.
We got a photo for our scrapbook before the legend himself takes the stage.
We have arrived to our final tourist attraction of this series.
And look at this.
Oh my gosh.
That's downtown Denver in the distance.
We were just there earlier.
This series would not have been possible without Shopify.
And I've had so much fun building my bucket list boxes with souvenirs and collectibles.
And the final step of building our store is to make it easy for our
customers to find it.
That's why I'm asking Sidekick for a domain name that's available, affordable, and makes sense
for our store.
Based on the options, I think we should go with BucketListBoxes.com.
I like that.
Luckily, Shopify makes it really easy to purchase a new domain.
And now our BucketListBox store is live.
There are only 10 boxes.
That's it.
As you saw in the last 10 episodes, it is so easy and fun to
build a store with Shopify.
And you can start your trial today at Shopify.com slash Ryan.
Thank you so much, Shopify.
It's time for the concert.
Gentlemen, I just went to the concession stand and got Haley and I hot dogs.
It's going to put a smile on her face.
It's the simple things, gentlemen.
Come on, gentlemen.
Watch this.
Hot dogs.
Alpha move.
Hot dogs and Red Rocks.
I love you, baby.
Gosh.
We have eaten more hot dogs in the past 10 days than most people eat
in a year.
I got this really cool time lapse as we waited for a couple hours for
Lewis Capaldi.
and as the rain came down, Haley felt validated.
Good thing I'm not in shorts.
Thank goodness Haley got jeans.
And suddenly, through the fog, Lewis Capaldi is ready to take the stage.
Something has happened.
Usually I'd be singing by now.
something technological has gone wrong he said he's gonna do the cool dramatic intro again
and that we're gonna act like the technical error never happened that's what's gonna happen
you never i was never here i love him yeah he's so funny and now
under the moonlight it's lewis capaldi time this is embarrassing
um lewis told us he's gonna perform acoustically which is fine by me.
He has an amazing voice.
Here we
go.
Wow, guys, here
we are.
The cinematic outro of the 2026 summer series.
The past two summers have been absolutely unforgettable.
Thanks to you, and thanks to my best friend.
Talking about Haley.
We have pretty much explored America to completion.
I am so grateful to be able to go on adventures like these and make
memories that we can share with our friends and family for decades.
But the real privilege is being able to share them with you.
And I mean that.
I remember when I started posting on this channel almost 10 years ago, I dreamed
of moments like this one, where I get to turn ideas into videos into memories.
We ranked Red Rocks at number seven and we completed our final stamp.
I'm going to miss doing this.
And that means our number one tourist attraction in America is the Grand Canyon.
Take care guys, see you soon.